Curriculum Vitæ for Gordon Reid

Personal Profile

I am a Computing Science graduate with an interest in both heterogeneous and distributed systems, specifically oriented around MPI and OpenCL.

I have working experience in a number of programming and scripting languages, including C, Java, OpenCL, Python, and a number of web technologies.

My current projects are available for viewing on my GitHub account: github.com/gordon1992

Contact information

Mobile: +44 7706 477 672

Personal Email: gordon.reid1992@hotmail.co.uk

Education

2010–2015 University of Glasgow MSci (Hons) Computing Science 1st Class

As part of the degree programme, I had two individual projects. The first involved parallelising a document filtering system by employing OpenCL to enable the system to make best use of the hardware available on heterogeneous systems. The second involved working torwards parallelisation and model coupling of existing Fortran simulations with a long term goal of automating as much of the work as possible.

Awards

June 2015 — Level 5 Honours Class Prize

June 2014 — Level 4 Honours Class Prize

June 2014 — BCS Prize for the project with the best evaluation

June 2013 — Level 3 Honours Class Prize

June 2012 — Level 2 Class Prize

Work Experience

August 2015 to Present — Software Development Engineer for Amazon

I rejoined the Dynamic Merchandising team I worked with during my internship working on projects relating to the new project I worked on during my internship.

June 2014 to August 2014 — Software Development Intern for Amazon

During the thirteen week internship I worked with the Dynamic Merchandising team. The work involved personalised and automated merchandising for Amazon's retail websites and mobile applications. I also worked on a new project, helping to bring it to its initial launch.

June 2013 to September 2013 — Summer IT Analyst for Morgan Stanley

During the thirteen week internship I was given the responsibility of my own project. I experienced the full software development life cycle from requirements gathering and analysis through to quality assurance entry and eventually to production.